Finding Aid for Warren Washburn Florer pamphlets and reprints, undated
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Warren Washburn Florer pamphlets and reprints undated and 1900-1932
Florer, Warren Washburn, 1869-
1 box
DA 2; F633; P186
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The provenance of this collection is unknown.
No further additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Warren W. Florer was a professor of German at the University of Michigan.
This is a collection of pamphlets and reprints of articles written by Warren W. Florer. The collection has been gathered together from different sources.
- Pamphlets and reprints
  - A guide for the Study of Heyse's L'Arrabbiata with Questions for Grammar Review, 1900 (Box 1)
  - A Guide for the Study of Riehl's Burg Neideck and von Jagemann's German Syntax, 1900 (Box 1)
  - Questions on Thomas's Grammar With Essentials of Grammar in German, 1903 (Box 1)
  - Remarks on the Direct Method of Teaching German, 1903 (Box 1)
  - Kapitel aus Luthers Bibeliübersetunzen (text ausgabe), 1904 (Box 1)
  - Report of the Meeting of the Modern Language Association, 1904 (Box 1)
  - The Importance of Contemporary German literature for the American student, 1905 (Box 1)
  - Report on some Eschenburg Manuscripts, 1909 (Box 1)
  - Luther's use of the Pre-Lutheran Versions of the Bible, 1911 (Box 1)
  - Luther's Use of the Bible in German Before 1522, 1912 (Box 1)
  - The Liberty Meeting in Detroit, December, 1851, 1932 (Box 1)
  - The American Revolution by Picture and Word, Ann Arbor and Michigan, undated (Box 1)
  - Essentials of Grammar, galley proofs, 3 sheets (Box 1)
  - Gender-change from Middle High German to Luther, as seen in the 1545 edition of the Bible, undated (Box 1)
  - Gustav Frenssen -- a study, undated (Box 1)
  - Luther's attitude toward language study, undated (Box 1)
  - Die Wichtigkeit der neuen deutschen Erziehund für America, undated (Box 1)